Previously on...
Tonight would be<br/>a great time
to tell Larry that you're<br/>not Jeff Strongman,
that you're really<br/>Alan Harper.
If you tell Larry<br/>who you really are,
then he's gonna wonder<br/>why I didn't tell him.
Will you do me the honor<br/>of becoming Mrs. Alan Harper?
Who the hell<br/>is Alan Harper?
Larry! Look! Boobs!
♪ Men. ♪
We can go in the other room and<br/>you can play with them. Huh?
Really?<br/>In the middle of the day?
Mm-hmm.
Wait a minute.<br/>Who's Alan Harper?
Uh, I am gonna answer that,<br/>but before I do...
What do you say, Gretchie?
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Oh, my God!
You've made me the-the<br/>happiest man in the world.
Don't cry. Don't cry.<br/>Don't cry.
A-And for your<br/>question, Larry,
I just want to say that<br/>everything you've known about me
is a lie.
My real name is Alan.
That's okay.<br/>My real name is Lawrence.
All right, this is gonna be<br/>a lot harder than I thought.
Um, uh, Lyndsey
is my ex-girlfriend.<br/>When you and she
got together,<br/>I made up a fake name
so that I could meet you<br/>and stay close to Lyndsey.
But then it turns out<br/>I actually like you
more than I like Lyndsey.
I like you<br/>more than Lyndsey, too!
What the hell<br/>is happening here?!
So your name's<br/>not really Jeff Strongman,
it's Alan Harper,<br/>and you used to date Lyndsey?
For four years.
Did you know about this?
Yes. He was my boyfriend.
But-but I'm with you now,<br/>and only you.
A-And I'm really, really sorry.
Oh, save it, Jeff--<br/>if that's even your real name.
I think I made it pretty clear<br/>it's not, but o-okay.
I told Alan that I thought<br/>he should tell you the truth,
because I thought<br/>you deserved to know.
How could you keep this from me?
I would never lie to you.<br/>This is unbelievable!
I never wanted<br/>any of this to happen.
Well, it did-- and now<br/>I've lost my two best friends.
And this time I'm not<br/>talking about your boobs.
I don't want to see<br/>either one of you again.
And I'm still not talking<br/>about your boobs!
The wedding's off!
Larry, wait!
Oh, God, see?
This is exactly why<br/>I didn't want to tell him.
Now both Lyndsey<br/>and Larry hate me,
and I've ruined the lives<br/>of two wonderful people.
I'll never forget<br/>the look on-- ooh, boobs.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,<br/>men, men ♪
♪ Ah.<br/>♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x22 ♪<br/>Oh WALD-E, Good Times Ahead<br/>Original Air Date on
== sync, corrected by elderman ==<br/>@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Say hello to my little friend.
What is that?
This is the most advanced
robotic artificial<br/>intelligence today.
I call him WALD-E.
Get it?
'Cause I'm Walden,
and the movie WALL-E?
WALD-E?
Say hello to my friend Jenny.
Hello to my friend Jenny.
I programmed him to be funny.
I beg to differ.
You're just jealous<br/>'cause you don't have
an electronic friend<br/>to play with.
Trust me, I have a whole drawer
of electronic friends<br/>I can play with.
Then maybe we can have<br/>a zero-one-one-way.
That's a three-way in binary.
Oh, WALD-E, good times ahead.
Hey.
Oh. Hey, check out<br/>my new robot.
I detect no sign<br/>of intelligent life.
I'm not in the mood for this.<br/>Can you turn him off?
Can you turn him off?
I wish I could, WALD-E,<br/>I wish I could.
What's going on?<br/>Larry just texted me.
He wants to see me.<br/>What do you think he wants?
Well,
given the fact<br/>you blew up his entire life,
I'm guessing he<br/>either wants to kick your ass,
or rip your face off so you<br/>can watch him kick your ass.
Oh, this is all my fault.
I should have just been honest
and told the truth<br/>right from the start--
lying is<br/>never the answer.
Ooh, I know,<br/>I'll tell him I'm sick.
What's a trendy illness?
Alan, you have to man up
and face the consequences<br/>of your actions.
Maybe you're right.
I at least owe him that much.
I'll just go and... Hah-choo!
Oh! Oh. Oh.
Alan?<br/>Mm-hmm?
When people sneeze,<br/>they don't say, "Hah-choo,
oh, ew, ooh."
Okay, fine.
But when he beats me<br/>within an inch of my life,
you're on bedpan duty.
Okay, if it makes you<br/>feel better, I'll come with you.
He only wants to<br/>go so when Larry beats you up,
he can say, "I told you so."
That is not true.
Even though<br/>I repeatedly
told him to stop lying<br/>about who he was,
and deceiving the people<br/>around him,
and eventually it<br/>would blow up in his face,
I'm not going to say,<br/>"I told you so."
Well, I appreciate that.
I want to film Larry<br/>kicking his ass
and then say,<br/>"I told you so""
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Alan.
Oh, hey,<br/>hey, Larry!
I don't have a weapon.
Hi. I'm Walden,
Alan's friend.
Uh, just act like I'm not here,
and punch like<br/>no one's watchin'.
And...
action.
So, you, uh, you said
you wanted to talk?
No, no, no, louder.
I'm sorry. What?
Louder. There's a lot<br/>of ambient noise in here.
So, so, you<br/>said you wanted to talk?
Yeah, I actually came here<br/>to tell you that I forgive you!
No! Cut! Cut!
What's... Wait, wait,<br/>you forgive him?
Yeah, I realized<br/>all this anger isn't good.
I had to let it all go.
No!
He's not gonna<br/>learn his lesson
if you forgive him.<br/>The only way he's gonna learn
a lesson is<br/>through pain and suffering
and possibly losing a tooth.
No, no. He's gonna be<br/>my brother-in-law
and make an honest woman<br/>out of Gretchen.
She's not gonna be an<br/>honest woman on our wedding night.
That's the guy I know and love<br/>who's banging my sister.
I do love banging<br/>your sister.
No, the only banging I want<br/>to see is you banging his face!
Oh,
that didn't come out right.
Gretchen is the most amazing<br/>woman I've ever met.
I-I just have to scrape together<br/>enough money for the wedding.
Oh, I know what you mean--<br/>mine and Lyndsey's
was costing me a fortune.
I already paid for the flowers,<br/>the cake, the tux.
Too bad you can't<br/>just take his wedding.
Or can I?
I was kidding.
Well, why not? I mean,<br/>this cup says "Peter" on it,
but Peter<br/>wasn't there to get it.
I'm not gonna use it.<br/>Me and Lyndsey are through,
so you might as well.
You can't mooch a wedding
that you just destroyed.
I know. How great is that?
Classic Alan Harper.
Jeff Strongman.<br/>Mm.
I don't know how<br/>I didn't see through it sooner.
It's such<br/>an obviously made-up name.
Yeah.<br/>Jeff.
♪ Men. ♪
Mom, this is my fiancée,<br/>Gretchen Martin.
It is so nice to finally<br/>meet you, Evelyn.
Oh, you, too, dear.
How far along are you?
What?<br/>Uh, my mother assumes that
since you agreed to marry me,<br/>you must be pregnant.
No, I'm not pregnant.
Are you after my money?<br/>Of course not.
¿Estas buscando trabajo<br/>en el mundo nuevo?
What?
Not looking<br/>for a green card, either.
You must genuinely like Alan.<br/>Yeah.
This is uncharted<br/>territory for me.
I know. She actually<br/>loves me for me.
I mean, I had to pretend<br/>to be another person
to make it all<br/>happen, but still.
Oh, that is some ring<br/>you bought her.
Oh, actually, that's the ring<br/>my ex-husband got me.
But I still had it-- I figured<br/>why make Alan buy another one?
My God, you've<br/>found your soul mate.
I know. Our honeymoon is<br/>at her cousin's time-share.
He can't use it, 'cause<br/>he had a heart attack.
We're so blessed.
Speaking of blessings,
I just want to thank you<br/>for raising such a caring,
thoughtful,<br/>intelligent son.
Oh, you're serious.
So, when's the big day?
Oh, uh, it's<br/>next Saturday.
We're just gonna have a small<br/>affair here at the house.
We're trying to<br/>keep costs down.
Are your parents coming?
Oh, no, my parents<br/>have passed away.
Again, we're<br/>so blessed.
So, where are you planning<br/>on living after you marry?
Oh, we're not in a rush<br/>to go anywhere.
I mean, beach house, no rent...
Don't be ridiculous--<br/>you need your own place.
Well, that's easier<br/>said than done, Mom.
How about for your wedding<br/>if I give you a down payment
towards your own...<br/>Oh, I love you, Mom!
I won't go that far,<br/>but thank you.
♪ Men. ♪
Walden.
Oh, don't worry,<br/>Alan's not with me.
Wow, it's amazing
how infrequently<br/>I actually get to say that.
What's up?
I just wanted<br/>to make sure you're okay.
That's sweet, but I'm fine.
When I get dumped, I usually<br/>end up sobbing in a bathtub,
listening to Michael Bublé.
I call it my "Bublé bath."
You sure you're all right?<br/>Yeah.
I was about to marry Larry,
a guy who once called<br/>venetian blind cleaners
because he wanted to help<br/>handicapped Italians.
Look, if Alan
and Gretchen are supposed<br/>to be together,
I wish them the best.
If you need anything,<br/>don't hesitate to call me.
Thanks.<br/>Okay.
Siri, remind me to draw<br/>a Bublé bath tonight.
Mm, what's that, Larry?
You forgive me<br/>and you still want to marry me?
Oh, Alan...
you never stopped loving me<br/>and you want to marry me, too?
I am the luckiest woman<br/>in the world.
♪ Men. ♪
Everybody, freeze.
What the hell?
Berta, I know<br/>where you hide your pot.
WALD-E!
No...!
Now, that's how you deal<br/>with a DEA drone.
No!
It's my robot!
I was playing a joke.
Oh.
It was funny.
Oh... oh...
Don't worry, little ro-buddy.
We'll get you on life support.
Or tech support.<br/>Oh, he would've loved that joke.
I lost the head<br/>of one of my toys once.
Of course, I had to go to the<br/>emergency room to get it out.
Um, listen, I know this<br/>may not be an opportune moment,
but, um, I was wondering,<br/>would you do me the honor of...
being my best man?
Of course. I would have<br/>been hurt if you didn't ask.
Oh, thanks, thanks. Great, man.
Uh, oh, and better get<br/>your speech ready
for the rehearsal dinner.
I'm taking everybody<br/>to Souplantation.
Fingers crossed we all end up<br/>at the same table.
Come on, come on,<br/>come on. We...
we got to go someplace fancier.
Well, I would love to,<br/>but I can't affo...
I'll pay for it.
Great. We've got reservations
at 7:30 at La Dolce.
♪ Men. ♪
I would like to make a toast<br/>to the bride and groom.
Um, I don't<br/>look at this
as losing a friend
so much as gaining a guest room.
I don't see this as<br/>losing a friend either.
Anyway, uh, to the happy couple.
Uh, Alan,
you're like a brother to me.
And, Gretchen,<br/>you...
have a smile that lights up<br/>those around you
and a heart big enough<br/>to let them all in.
So...
cheers.
That was so sweet.
Is he gay?
If he was, you think<br/>I'd be with you right now?
♪ Men. ♪
Um, occupied.
Ocupado.
S-Sprechen Sie poopin.
Alan.
Lyndsey?!
I need to talk to you.
You scared the crap out of me.<br/>Literally.
This'll just take a sec.
Wh-What are you doing?
My whole family's here<br/>in the restaurant.
I'm here to say yes.
To what?
Your proposal.
I want to be your wife.
I am yours forever<br/>and ever and ever.
I am crazy for you.
Oh, I don't doubt that.
You know you still want me.
Fate has brought us here<br/>together.
Uh, actually,<br/>my lactose intolerance
has brought us here together.
Whatever. It was meant to be.
Um, Lyndsey, Lyndsey,
a-as romantic as this moment is,
um, uh, I-I'm in love<br/>with Gretchen.
What happened to me?
I was the prize.
Men were fighting over me.
Am I not hot anymore?
Oh, I'm gonna need that.
Here.
They're sanitized<br/>for your protection.
Look, I-I still care<br/>about you and...
Oh, stop it.
I don't want your pity.
I'm gonna get out of here<br/>while I still have my dignity.
Oh, great.
Now everyone at the table's<br/>gonna know I was pooping.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Alan,
I have a little surprise<br/>for your big day.
Oh! Cash or check?
I brought Jake to the wedding.
My son. Yes. Yes.
Yes, that's-that's way better<br/>than cash.
Um, uh, where is he?
Hi, Dad.
Pull my finger.
Classic Robot Jake.
Alan, can I see you a second?
Oh, did you see Jake came<br/>to the wedding?
Sure, of course. Hello, Jake.
Hey, Larry.
Hey.
You're looking...<br/>pretty pensive.
Oh, thanks, it's a rental.
You look pretty<br/>pensive, too.
Actually...
Thank you.
Uh, hey, I just wanted<br/>to say that it's, um....
it's pretty big of you<br/>to forgive Alan the way you did.
I mean,
after hearing that he was<br/>still sleeping with Lyndsey
when you two<br/>were dating...
...is apparently something<br/>you're hearing
for the first time<br/>right now.
Are you freakin' kidding me?<br/>They were cheating?!
I'll kill him!
Larry, Larry,
I'm sorry.<br/>For what?
This.
Okay, let's get this show<br/>on the road!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.<br/>What-What's the rush?
Oh, uh,<br/>I accidentally told Larry
that you and Lyndsey<br/>were cheating on him,
so he wanted to kill you<br/>so I pushed him off the deck.
Let's go! Showtime!<br/>Chop, chop! Come on!
Oh,
wow, so pensive.
Where's my brother?
Oh.
Uh,
he was overcome with emotion.
So he hit the beach.
Uh, but don't worry.<br/>I'm filming it.
Oh, by the way,<br/>if you trip on your dress
and accidentally flash us,<br/>just go with it.
A-All right, honey,<br/>you look beautiful,
but let's move it along, please.
Uh, Jenny, hit it.
"Daughters, mothers, sisters,<br/>we gather here,
safe from the patriarchy and the<br/>oppression of its penises..."
Oh, I really should've<br/>revised this
before doing a straight wedding.
Um, wh-why don't we, uh, skip<br/>to the vows that you guys wrote?
All right. Um...
I, Gretchen, do swear<br/>to honor and cherish you.
You asked me to go down<br/>the road of life with you,
and I am answering.
I will go down.
That's what she said.
And I, Alan, do swear to honor,
cherish and stand behind you
whether things are easy
or things are hard.
That's what he said.
Alan, do you take Gretchen<br/>to be your...
I object!
Lyndsey?
Lyndsey, Lyndsey,<br/>you can't be here.
Aren't I a pretty, pretty bride,<br/>Alan?
Yes.
You look insanely<br/>beautiful.
Uh, now let's<br/>turn you around
and get you in a<br/>cab. How 'bout...
No!
This was supposed to be my day!
My wedding!
My groom!
My f... Wait.
Those are my flowers.
That's my food!
Those are my linens.
That's my...
I think<br/>she was gonna say "cake"!
I always liked her.
So, uh...<br/>so where were we?
Gretchen?
Derek?
Who's this guy?
He's my ex-husband.
Oh, come on!
What are you doing here?
Some crazy lady called and said<br/>you were getting married.
Well,<br/>actually,
what she said was,
"Gretchen, pretty, pretty brid""
followed by two minutes<br/>of intense vomiting.
Pretty sure<br/>that was her.
Boo-ya!
Gretchen, I know I made<br/>some horrible mistakes.
I drank too much,<br/>I wrecked your truck,
I cheated on you<br/>with your best friend.
In your truck.<br/>While I was drunk.
Which is why<br/>I wrecked it.
Lose your dog<br/>and you got a country song.
I wouldn't know.<br/>I'm more into hip-hop.
I miss you, baby.<br/>I want you back.
Hey, Derek,
if you want her back,
you're gonna have<br/>to go through me.
Fine by me.
And him.
Look, seeing you in that<br/>white dress right before
I beat up two goobers<br/>reminds me of our wedding.
But this time the cake's not<br/>in the shape of Dale Jr.,
which is a<br/>huge oversight.
Derek...
You're not actually<br/>considering this, are you?
I don't know. I'm so confused.
I mean, Derek and I have<br/>so much history together.
This is really hard.
That's what she said.
That's what they say.
I'm sorry, Alan. I-I at least<br/>have to talk to him.
Gretchen, wait!
It's times like this<br/>a son needs his mother.
I'm gonna slip out<br/>the back.
Serves you right,<br/>you bastard.
I mean, I love you.
Let's work this out.
Best wedding ever!
Yep! And I got<br/>the whole thing on...
Aw, crap, I had it on photo.
♪ Men. ♪
How you doing?
I've had better days.
Hey, I'm sorry, buddy.
Later, I'll run<br/>you a Bublé bath.
Thanks.
Gretchen called.
She said it's not over.
She's just sorting things out.
Oh, buddy.
"Sorting things out"<br/>is just people's way
of not giving you bad news.
So I take it your...
mom's not gonna give you the<br/>money for your own place?
I'm just sorting<br/>things out.
You know what?
I didn't really want<br/>you to leave anyway.
Aw. Thanks.
Can you believe it?
We're still together,<br/>three years later.
I know.
I thought for sure<br/>it was over when Charlie died.
Thank God I showed up.
You're telling me.<br/>Hmm.
I... You know,<br/>I've been so busy lately.
I-I really miss<br/>hanging out with you.
Yeah. Me, too. You know,<br/>we should pick a night
where we just<br/>always get together.
No matter what's going on,<br/>once a week, we just do this.
Okay, I like it.<br/>I like it.
How 'bout, uh, here<br/>every Thursday night?
9:00.
It's a date.
Uh, don't call it a date.
Just call it...<br/>two men hanging out.
Hey.
What about me?
Okay, fine.<br/>Two and a half men.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==<br/>@elder_man